livesport.tv 2018-06-29

# Watch Live Sport | Stream Football, Boxing, Cricket + More Online

This Privacy Policy explains how Perform Media Channels Limited (" **Perform** ") together with other companies within the Perform Group(which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006) (the " **Perform Group** ") use information we collect about you and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

Unless separately defined herein, the defined terms in this Privacy Policy have the same meaning as in the Terms and Conditions which can be found [here](http://www.livesport.tv/contact-us/terms-of-use)

By your use of the Website you consent to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

Additionally, the Website contains links to websites that are not operated by Perform Group. These third parties may collect data from you and share some of that data with us. Perform Group are careful when choosing their partners, sponsors, and affiliates, but Perform Group are not responsible for any misuse of personal information by such third parties.We recommend that you view the Privacy Policy posted on each Website that you use to confirm that the companies' policies are acceptable to you.

1\. PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION AND HOW IT IS USED

When using the Services, we may ask you to provide all or some of the following information: your name, your address, your email address, banking details, your telephone number, and your age (" **Personal Information** "). We may also ask you to provide your thoughts or answer some questions about your favourite events, personalities, and other subjects of interest to sports fans. 

In order to purchase any live events viewable on this Website, participate in any contest or message feature, download any content, take part in any other interactive feature of the Websites, or receive information from Perform Group, such as newsletters or email regarding upcoming the Services you must register and provide accurate information about yourself to the Websites, as the Services may not work properly without such information.

We may use the Personal Information you provide to us to do some or all of the following: 

-provide you with personalised visits to our site;

-recommend goods, services or promotions which may be of interest to you (but only where you have requested us to do so);

-develop our offers and the layout of our site to ensure that our services are as useful and enjoyable as possible;

-contact you in order to conduct market research; and

-send out email alerts you may have signed up for.

Perform Group will not, however, sell or lease your Personal Information to third parties not associated with Perform Group, its partners, sponsors, and affiliates.

If you do not wish to receive marketing and promotional communications from us or our partners, sponsors, and affiliates, you can choose to opt-out when providing your Personal Information to Perform Group. You can also opt-out by updating your user profile on the Website. 

Please note: If you do decide to opt-out of receiving information, Perform Group will be unable to keep you informed of any new products, services, or special offers that may interest you and will have an impact on our ability to inform you of any live events or important information as part of any subscription service you may have.

2\. SECURITY

We understand that the security of your Personal Information is important to you.When handling Personal Information, security is paramount and we have in place a security policy which ensures that Personal Information is adequately protected.Your Personal Information is password protected, and any Personal Information you provide to Perform Group is protected from unauthorised disclosure by reasonable technological measures. However, some limited Personal Information provided to Perform Group is transmitted using unencrypted protocols. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. 

3\. AGGREGATED INFORMATION

To evaluate the Websites and ensure that we are providing Content and Services of interest to you, we may collect and store statistical information regarding how you use the Websites, the name of your internet service provider, any websites that referred you to the Websites, and the time and date you view the Websites. We may also use Personal Information to develop demographic information regarding Website users. Such aggregated information will not identify you personally. We may share this aggregated, statistical information with our partners, sponsors, affiliates, and other third parties.

We may on occasion combine information we receive online with other records to enhance our ability to notify you of our products and services that we think will be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive these notifications please send an e-mail to [customerservices@performgroup.com](mailto:customerservices@performgroup.com) letting us know.

4\. COOKIES

﻿We use cookies in order to ensure the website functions properly and to improve your user experience. Cookies are usually a string of numbers and/or letters that a website transfers to your hard drive. The cookies enable the website to "remember" you, either for the duration of your visit (session cookies) or for repeat visits (persistent cookies). We recommend that you visit the websites [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and [www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/) if you would like in-depth information about cookies.

On this website, we use the following types of cookies:

**Strictly necessary cookies**

| 

These cookies are essential to enable you to navigate around the site securely and to provide you with services you have specifically requested. For instance, they help ensure that payments are processed securely.  
  
---|---  
  
**Functionality cookies**

| 

These cookies enhance the functionality of the website by storing your preferences. For instance, they can remember your name and location, if you provide this information.  
  
**Performance cookies**

| 

These cookies improve the performance of the website. For instance, they help pages load quicker.  
  
**Online behavioural cookies**

| 

These cookies store information about your behaviour online, such as your browsing history. For instance, they help us tailor the advertising we show to you to your interests.  
  
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can change your browser to prevent that. You are not obliged to accept cookies and you can adjust your browser's setting to prevent it from accepting cookies on your computer - go to www.cookiecentral.com for instructions on how to disable cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of our site or use certain functions if you disable cookies. 

If you register with us or if you continue to use our site, you agree to our use of cookies.

5\. DISCLOSURE FOR LAW ENFORCEMENT PURPOSES

Perform Group reserve the right to access and disclose Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and lawful government requests, to operate its systems properly, or to protect itself or others. Perform Group may attempt to obtain the prior consent of the individual before disclosing the Personal Information, but it has no obligation to do so.

6\. PARENTS & GUARDIANS

This Website is a general audience Website. We do not knowingly collect and/or share Personal Information from children under the age of thirteen on the Website. However, your child cannot use some of the interactive features of the Website without providing Personal Information. We therefore recommend using the Website with your child if he or she is interested in participating in an interactive feature of the Website.

If, in the future, Perform Group actively collects Personal Information from children, it will do so in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998.

7\. ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION

Data Protection law gives you various rights including the right to access the Personal Information that is held about you.

We, as data controller, are required to provide you with copies of all the Personal Information we hold about you, on payment of a nominal administration charge of £10.If you wish to access the Personal Information held by us, you should therefore contact us at [customerservices@performgroup.com](mailto:customerservices@performgroup.com).

You can also request at any time that the Personal Information we hold about you is updated or corrected.

8\. YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS

If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, the changes will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. We will not use or disclose Personal Information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without informing you and providing you with an opportunity to opt-out of these unrelated uses.

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy please feel free to contact us at [customerservices@performgroup.com](mailto:customerservices@performgroup.com)

Registered Office:

Perform Media Channels Limited

Sussex House

Plane Tree Crescent

Feltham TW13 7HE

Tel: (0)20 3372 0600

Registered No: 5645564
